<?xml version='1.0'?>
<game_locations>
	<location ID="1" Visited="0">
		<North>3</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>2</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Front Walk</Name>
		<Description>
You are standing in front of a large white house. Next to you is a small
mailbox. It is an old fashioned mailbox, the kind that you might see standing
next to a farmhouse out in the country somewhere. The only thing is, this is
the city. The mailbox just doesn't belong here. Oh, and it is purple! Yes, it
is purple and it has white flowers on it.

Your car is parked at the curb. Unfortunately, in your haste to get out of the
car, you locked your keys and your phone inside. Good luck with that.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="2" Visited="0">
		<North>9</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>1</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Driveway</Name>
		<Description>
The driveway is paved with concrete rather than blacktop. It is generally
in good repair but there are a few cracks and, here and there, blades of
grass have grown up through the cracks.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="3" Visited="0">
		<North>4</North>
		<South>1</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Front Porch</Name>
		<Description>
The front porch is small. There is only enough room for one or two people to
stand in front of the door. Strangely enough, there is another mailbox here.
This one is the kind they normally have on city homes. Unfortunately, someone
has been messing around and it is hanging by one nail. It is clearly empty. The
front door is white, with nine small pains of glass. You might try to look in,
but the panes of glass are pebbled, so that you can only sense light and shadow
on the other side. I suppose it was a privacy measure.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="4" Visited="0">
		<North>10</North>
		<South>3</South>
		<East>5</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>11</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Entry Hall</Name>
		<Description>
Entry Hall is a grand term for such a small space. The area is just large
enough to contain a small closet. Straight ahead, a small door opens into
a powder room. To the left is a staircase leading up to the second floor. At
the bottom of the stairs, there is a bookcase filled with DVDs and Blu-Rays.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="5" Visited="0">
		<North>6</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>4</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Living Room</Name>
		<Description>
The Living Room is large. It contains two full-sized couches and a recliner.
There is a fireplace in the center of the East wall. Next to the fireplace is
a large-screen television. On the north end of the room an archway leads into
the Dining Room. The south end of the room is dominated by a bay window.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="6" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>5</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>7</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Dining Room</Name>
		<Description>
The Dining Room is just large enough to hold a hardwood table and eight
massive chairs. The charis are made of dark wood and are ornately carved. Two
pairs of cabinets on the back wall flank a framed print of "The Knighting."
The table is clear, except for a blue pillar candle.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="7" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>8</South>
		<East>6</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Kitchen</Name>
		<Description>
The kitchen is small but efficiently laid out. The refrigerator is a side-
by-side model with a brushed aluminum front. The countertop surfaces are
black marble. A double sink under the north window gives you a view of the
backyard, an overgrown mass of tall grass dotted here and there with Queen
Anne's Lace.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="8" Visited="0">
		<North>7</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>9</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>21</Down>
		<Name>Laundry Room</Name>
		<Description>
The Laundry Room is even smaller than the Entry Hall. A washer and dryer stand
on the east wall. The West wall contains a door that leads to the garage and
a flight of stairs leads down to what is probably the basement.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="9" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>2</South>
		<East>8</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Garage</Name>
		<Description>
The Garage runs the length of the house and contains an eclectic collection of
tools. A workbench dominates the West wall. The light is one, apparently it has
been burning since your Aunt was in residence. You might wonder what she was
doing with all such a huge tool collection, but you have to hand her credit for
having good taste.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="10" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>4</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Powder Room</Name>
		<Description>
The Powder Room is small. There is only enough room for a toilet and a sink.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="11" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>14</East>
		<West>12</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>4</Down>
		<Name>Upstairs Landing</Name>
		<Description>
You are at the top of the stairs, just outside what seems to be a home office.
The halway to the east has several doors opening off it and another door at
the opposite end of the hall opens into a slightly larger bathroom. A sign on
the door outside the office says, "Irene's Office"
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="12" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>11</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Irene's Office</Name>
		<Description>
Whoever Irene is, she has a really nice home office. Built-in bookcases lineage
both sides of an alocve that leads to a narrow window on the south side of the
room. The West wall has two broad windows, one of which has an air conditioning
unit. A large multi-leveled desk is situated in the northwest corner of the
room. The corner has been painted with purple chalkboard paint which has been
covered with notes and what look like drawings of the user interface for
computer applications. The desk has three monitors two on the upper level and
off to the left on the lower level. There is a large-screen TV in the southeast
corner of the room. The TV is on an entertainment center and you can see
several gaming consoles and a Blu-Ray player on the stand underneath the TV.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="13" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>16</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Warren's Office</Name>
		<Description>
This room is a home office. It contains an L-shaped desk, and yet another
large-screen TV. The rest of the available space in this room has been devoted
to bookcases. The collection of books is large and varied.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="14" Visited="0">
		<North>15</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>16</East>
		<West>11</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Hallway (West End)</Name>
		<Description>
You are now standing in front of a door that says, "Matt's Place." You can
enter the room, which is on the north side of the hall, or you can continue
to the end of the hall where there are three doors leading to the north,
south, and east.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="15" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>14</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Matt's Room</Name>
		<Description>
This room has been painted a bright, cheerful blue. The room contains one
of those beds that has three drawers underneath it. The room also contains a
computer desk with a single screen and a desktop computer. Opposite the beds
is yet another large-screen TV and several more video game consoles. Clearly
there were people other than your Aunt living here and they loved movies and
video games.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="16" Visited="0">
		<North>13</North>
		<South>18</South>
		<East>17</East>
		<West>14</West>
		<Up>20</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Hallway (East End)</Name>
		<Description>
The east end of the hall features three doors and an overhead trapdoor that
most likely leads to the attic.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="17" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>16</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Main Bathroom</Name>
		<Description>
This bathroom is larger than the one downstairs. It has a large vanity with
a mirrored medicine cabinet above it. Behind a shower curtain with a lighthouse
motif, you find a small bathtub. A small window on the east side of the room
looks out onto the neighbor's house.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="18" Visited="0">
		<North>16</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>19</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Master Bedroom</Name>
		<Description>
This is clearly the master bedroom. A queen-sized bed dominates the room,
leaving room for a triple dresser on the north wall, and a tall dresser on the
south wall. On top of the dresser is (you guess it!) yet another large-screen
TV with a Blu-Ray player. A door on the west wall leads into the master bath.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="19" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>18</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Master Bathroom</Name>
		<Description>
The master bathroom contains a large shower stall with multiple shower heads.
There is a small cabinet over the toilet, and a medicine cabinet over the sink.
Other than that, htere is very little of interest in this room.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="20" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>0</Up>
		<Down>16</Down>
		<Name>Attic</Name>
		<Description>
The attic doesn't have a floor. However, in several sections, 4' by 8' panels
have been laid on the joists to provide storage space. Quite a few large
cardboard boxes have been stored here.
		</Description>
	</location>
	<location ID="21" Visited="0">
		<North>0</North>
		<South>0</South>
		<East>0</East>
		<West>0</West>
		<Up>8</Up>
		<Down>0</Down>
		<Name>Basement</Name>
		<Description>
The basement was obviously devote to storage. In addition to the furnace and
hot water heater, you find an upright freezer and shelves stocked with canned
goods. On the east wall, someone has stacked at least 20 or more cardboard
boxes on pallets. In the northwest corner of the room is an opening in the
floor where you can see a sump pump.
		</Description>
	</location>
</game_locations>